3b7b
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>iphone jailbreak &#8211; GaDgetHackz</title>
	<atom:link href="https://gadgethackz.tk/tag/iphone-jailbreak/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://gadgethackz.tk</link>
	<description>Gadget Hacks » Smartphone Lifehacks, Guides, Tips, Tricks &#38; How-Tos</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 10:12:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Hexxa Plus Online Jailbreak is just released for iOS 13.5.1</title>
		<link>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hexxa-plus-online-jailbreak-is-just-released-for-ios-13-5-1/</link>
					<comments>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hexxa-plus-online-jailbreak-is-just-released-for-ios-13-5-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siteadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 09:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how to jailbreak ios 13 with hexa plux]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone 13]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone jailbreak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[no computer jailbreak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uncover jailbreak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uncover jailbreak for ios 13.5]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[with out computer iphone jailbreak]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gadgethackz.tk/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Install awesome jailbreak Apps, collection of themes, you can alos install the apps banned from app store.its also good if you want to install + Install Awesome Jailbreak apps + &#8230; <a href="https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hexxa-plus-online-jailbreak-is-just-released-for-ios-13-5-1/" class="more-link">Read More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Install awesome jailbreak Apps, collection of themes, you can alos install the apps banned from app store.its also good if you want to install </p>



<p>+ Install Awesome Jailbreak apps</p>



<p>+ Collection of Themes</p>



<p>+ App store banned apps/games</p>



<p>+ Premium ++ Apps</p>



<p>+ Game Emulators</p>



<p> </p>



<p>Apple fixed unc0ver Jailbreak releasing iOS 13.5.1. However, Hexxa Plus repo extractor was released for iOS 13.5.1. Now you can install jailbreak apps / tweaks for iOS 13.5.1 extracting Jailbreak repos.</p>



<p>Hexxa Plus is different from Unc0ver semi untethered Jailbreak. Hexxa Plus Installation process is so much easier than IPA based Unc0ver or checkm8 based Checkrain. But all system related Jailbreak apps and tweaks are not available for iOS 13.5.1 via Hexxa Plus.</p>



<p><strong><a href="https://hexxaplus.com/install/latest/app/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">DOWONLOAD HEXA PLUS</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Hexaa+ iOS 13 Jailbreak (New Update) 2019" width="1170" height="658" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YhFFf5fctVM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>Currently Hexxa Plus is the only iOS 13.5.1 Jailbreak solution. You can install so many Jailbreak apps, tweaks and themes using this. Now it is compatible to install jailbreak apps for iOS 14 as well.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Compatibility&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>iPhone 11, 11 pro, 11 pro max, iPhone Xs, iPhone Xs Max, iPhone Xr, iPhone X, iPhone 8, iPhone 8 Plus, Phone 7 &amp; 7 Plus, iPhone 6S &amp; 6S Plus, iPhone 6 &amp; 6 Plus, iPhone SE, iPad Mini (5th gen), iPad Air (2019, 3rd gen), iPad Pro 2nd gen &amp; 1st gen, iPad Pro, iPad Air 2, iPad Air, iPad 6th gen, iPad 5th gen, iPad mini 4, iPad mini 3, iPad mini 2, iPod Touch 6G</p>



<ul><li>Hexxa Plus is not a semi untethered or tethered Jailbreak solution. That’s mean It doesn’t affect your iOS system room.&nbsp;</li><li>Hexxa Plus is compatible with all latest device models such as iPhone 11 series and iPhone XS series.</li><li>You don’t need to use a computer, iTunes or Cydia impactor to install Hexxa Plus. There is no IPA sideload process. Hexxa Plus is a completely online jailbreak solution.&nbsp;</li><li>Hexxa Plus is a 100% risk free iOS 13.5.1 jailbreak solution. You can uninstall / reinstall it any time. Also, no crash your iOS device once reboot.&nbsp;</li><li>Hexxa Plus does not void your iOS device warranty.&nbsp;</li><li>Recently, Hexxa Plus upgraded, adding many new repostaries. You can install many Jailbreak apps and tweaks using these repostaries.</li></ul>



<h2><strong>Unc0ver Jailbreak for iOS 13.5.1</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/uncover1351.png" alt="" class="wp-image-8" width="922" height="346" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/uncover1351.png 800w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/uncover1351-300x113.png 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/uncover1351-768x288.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 922px) 100vw, 922px" /></figure>



<p>pple fixed the uncover Jailbreak for iOS 13.5.1 releasing iOS 13.5.1 version. Now Unc0ver latest version doesn’t support iOS 13.5.1. However, the Unc0ver team is working on a new Unc0ver exploit that could jailbreak iOS 13.5.1.</p>



<p>Uncover is the most popular Jailbreak tool since iOS 11. However, when it comes to iOS 13 – iOS 13.5 Jailbreak it has some issues. There is no Online jailbreak which properly works. It is getting revoked issues. Also, it has a complicated JB process using the alt store on Mac &amp; Windows users. Also, it should have an Apple developer account to complete the Jailbreak method for linux users to work with the Cydia Impactor.</p>



<p><strong>CheckRain Jailbreak for iOS 13.5.1</strong></p>



<p>Checkra1n is hardware based jailbreak for iOS 12.3 – iOS 13.5 jailbreak. This works with iOS 13.5.1 too because it can not be fixed via software update. They will add iOS 13.5.1 jailbreak support via next checkra1n 0.10.3 beta officially.</p>



<p>One of the reasons for jailbreaking is to expand the feature set limited by Apple and its App Store.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-ars-2">[2]</a></sup> Apple checks apps for compliance with its iOS Developer Program License Agreement before accepting them for distribution in the App Store. However, their reasons for banning apps are not limited to safety and security and may be regarded as arbitrary and capricious.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-3">[3]</a></sup> In one case, Apple mistakenly banned an app by a Pulitzer-Winning cartoonist because it violated its developer license agreement, which specifically bans apps that &#8220;contain content that ridicules public figures.&#8221;<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-4">[4]</a></sup> To access banned apps,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-5">[5]</a></sup> users rely on jailbreaking to circumvent Apple&#8217;s censorship of content and features. Jailbreaking permits the downloading of programs not approved by Apple,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-6">[6]</a></sup> such as user interface customization and tweaks.</p>



<h3>Device customization</h3>



<p>Since software programs available through <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/APT_(Package_Manager)">APT</a> and or <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Installer.app">Installer.app</a> (legacy) are not required to adhere to App Store guidelines, many of them are not typical self-contained apps but instead are extensions and customization options for iOS and its features and other apps (commonly called tweaks).<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-lifehacker-dachis-7">[7]</a></sup> Users install these programs for purposes including personalization and customization of the interface by tweaks developed by developers and designers,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-lifehacker-dachis-7">[7]</a></sup> adding desired features such as access to the root file system and fixing annoyances,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-nytimes-8">[8]</a></sup> and making development work on the device easier by providing access to the filesystem and command-line tools.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-9">[9]</a></sup><sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-10">[10]</a></sup> Many Chinese iOS device owners also jailbreak their phones to install third-party <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chinese_input_methods_for_computers">Chinese</a> character <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Input_method">input systems</a> because they are easier to use than Apple&#8217;s.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-11">[11]</a></sup></p>



<h3>Carrier unlocking</h3>



<p>Jailbreaking also opens the possibility for using <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Software">software</a> to unofficially unlock <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SIM_lock">carrier-locked</a> iPhones so they can be used with other carriers.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-12">[12]</a></sup> Software-based unlocks have been available since September 2007,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-13">[13]</a></sup> with each tool applying to a specific iPhone model and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baseband_processor">baseband</a> version (or multiple models and versions).<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-14">[14]</a></sup> This includes the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_4S">iPhone 4S</a>, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_4">iPhone 4</a>, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_3GS">iPhone 3GS</a>, and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_3G">iPhone 3G</a> models. An example of unlocking an iPhone through a Jailbreak utility would be Redsn0w. Through this software, iPhone users will be able to create a custom <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPSW">IPSW</a> and unlock their device. Moreover, during the unlocking process, there are options to install Cydia the iPad baseband.</p>



<h3>Installation of malware</h3>



<p>Computer criminals may jailbreak an iPhone to install malware or target jailbroken iPhones on which malware can be installed more easily. The Italian cybersecurity company Hacking Team, which sells hacking software to law enforcement agencies, advised police to jailbreak iPhones to allow tracking software to be installed on them.</p>



<h3>Software piracy</h3>



<p>On iPhones, the installation of consumer software is generally restricted to installation through the App Store. Jailbreaking, therefore, allows the installation of pirated applications.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-17">[17]</a></sup> It has been suggested that a major motivation for Apple to prevent jailbreaking is to protect the income of its App Store, including third-party developers and allow the buildup of a sustainable market for third-party software.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-18">[18]</a></sup> However, the installation of pirated applications is also possible without jailbreaking, taking advantage of enterprise certificates to facilitate distribution of modified or pirated releases of popular applications</p>



<p></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/check1351-1024x384-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-9" width="927" height="348" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/check1351-1024x384-1.png 1024w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/check1351-1024x384-1-300x113.png 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/check1351-1024x384-1-768x288.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 927px) 100vw, 927px" /></figure>



<p>However, it has some limitations. This checkra1n works only for A5-A11 devices. Latest iPhone 11 models and iPhone Xs models do not work with Checkra1n. On the other hand, there is no online jailbreak method for Checkra1n. Also, Windows users have to use alternative complicated method to run checkra1n Jailbreak process.</p>



<h2><strong>without computer or No Computer online Jailbreak</strong></h2>



<p>Hexxa plus is the only online jailbreak solution for iOS 13.5.1.</p>



<p>Apple blocks online plist IPA for semi-untethered Jailbreak. Once reported, these signing services to Apple, the company immediately revoked licenses. Once these licenses are revoked, it is required to set up a new account to resign every application on that platform. This process takes a long time.</p>



<p>At this moment, all unc0ver enterprise certificates are revoked and blocked by Apple. Many websites such as silzee, ignition.fun, tweakbox have stopped providing enterprise certificate based online Jailbreak. So, no computer;online Jailbreak for previous Unc0ver versions too.&nbsp;</p>



<p>So if unc0ver releases iOS 13.5.1 Jailbreak, permanent online Jailbreaking will be almost impossible.</p>



<p>Last Unc0ver Jailbreak works with Windows, Mac with the Altstore and Cydia impactor. Also, linux works only with Cydia impactor. You need to sideload the IPA using Altstore or Cydia impactor. Both this method required Computer. This Altstore is introduced because Cydia impactor works with Paid Certificate only. So, you need an Apple developer account. Linux users have no other option except Cydia impactor.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Checkra1n is a computer based Jailbreak. There is No Computer online Jailbreak for CheckRa1n.Mac users have to download the Checkra1n dmg file and Connect the Mac and the device.&nbsp; Then it should recognize the device going through&nbsp; Mac’s application folder &gt; checkra1n &gt; Contents &gt; MacOS &gt; Checkra1n_gui Terminal file. Once done it can complete the jailbreak process with DFU mode.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Also, Linux users have to download the linux file according to the computer version and run commands using the terminal window. Windows users have to years alternative methods somewhat hard Ra1nUSB, Ra1nstorm, Bootra1n or pira1n. Ultimately we can not expect CheckRa1n online jailbreak for iOS 13.5.1 versions too.&nbsp;</p>

f3
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hexxa-plus-online-jailbreak-is-just-released-for-ios-13-5-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

0

