42f5
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>siteadmin &#8211; GaDgetHackz</title>
	<atom:link href="https://gadgethackz.tk/author/siteadmin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://gadgethackz.tk</link>
	<description>Gadget Hacks » Smartphone Lifehacks, Guides, Tips, Tricks &#38; How-Tos</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:37:19 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>what 5g+ icon Shown in your status bar really-means</title>
		<link>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/what-5g-icon-shown-in-your-status-bar-really-means/</link>
					<comments>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/what-5g-icon-shown-in-your-status-bar-really-means/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siteadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:34:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[SMART PHONES]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g availablilty]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g configurations]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g extrea speed]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g how to activate on your android]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g icon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g network]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g signal enhancement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[5g signal improvement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[smartphones]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gadgethackz.tk/?p=26</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Conclusions. Over-exposure to any man made technologies could potentially be harmful and 5G is not unique. However, 5G is no more or less safe compared to 4G or 3G or &#8230; <a href="https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/what-5g-icon-shown-in-your-status-bar-really-means/" class="more-link">Read More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p></p>



<p><img class="wp-image-27" style="width: 570px;" src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/125g.png" alt="">Conclusions. Over-exposure to any man made technologies could potentially be <strong>harmful</strong> and <strong>5G</strong> is not unique. However, <strong>5G</strong> is no more or less safe compared to 4G or 3G or even your home wifi. <strong>5G</strong> did not cause Coronavirus COVID-19 and it did not contribute to the spread of the pandemic in any way,3GPP (the folks who created the 5G standard) opted for multiple ranges of frequencies to provide 5G. This was the best solution for carriers, as they were able to roll out 5G in a way that was both fast and less costly. Unfortunately, these frequencies provide a different experience on 5G, resulting in multiple icons.</p>



<p>Whenever you look at the top corner of your phone, what do you see? Upon upgrading to Android 11 or iOS 14, you&#8217;ll see either &#8220;5G,&#8221; &#8220;5G+,&#8221; or &#8220;5G E&#8221; if you&#8217;re connected to the right network. But what exactly do these symbols mean? They indicate not only <em>if</em> you&#8217;re using 5G, but also what <em>type</em> you&#8217;re connected to.</p>



<h2>The Different 5G Icons</h2>



<p><img class="wp-image-28" style="width: 150px;" src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/5g-2-512.png" alt="" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/5g-2-512.png 512w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/5g-2-512-300x300.png 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/5g-2-512-150x150.png 150w" sizes="(max-width: 512px) 100vw, 512px" />If your phone has a 5G modem, you will see one of two symbols: <strong>5G</strong> or <strong>5G+</strong>. 5G means your phone is currently connected to 5G NR on a sub-6 GHz frequency. Bands in this range provide better coverage but slower speeds. The higher the frequency, the faster your download speeds.</p>



<p>Unfortunately, this icon won&#8217;t tell you if you are connected to low-band (less than 1 GHz) or a mid-band (1–7.125 GHz) 5G, but a quick speed test will give you a rough idea, as low band gets download speeds of 30–250 Mbps and mid-band gets 100–900 Mbps.</p>



<p>T-Mobile has been adding this icon on their phones even when they are not connected to the 5G network, so if you are unsure, download the app Signal Spy (on Android) or enter Field Test Mode on your iPhone to see what connection you have.<img class="wp-image-29" style="width: 500px;" src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/android-v-ios-apps-720x720-1.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/android-v-ios-apps-720x720-1.jpg 720w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/android-v-ios-apps-720x720-1-300x200.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 720px) 100vw, 720px" /></p>



<p>Then there is <strong>5G+</strong>. If you happen to be lucky enough to see this symbol in your status bar, rejoice — you have access to a multi-gigabit connection. 5G+ indicates you&#8217;re connected to a mm Wave 5G NR tower, short-range radios that deliver breakneck speeds. Performing a speed test will reveal download speeds of <strong>1–3 Gbps</strong>. For context, 4G LTE averages around 0.025 Gbps on most US carriers.</p>



<p>For those on Verizon, you may see <strong>5G UWB</strong> in the status bar. This is the marketing name for its mm Wave network and is the same as 5G+.</p>



<h2>What About 5G E?</h2>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="How 5G works and what it delivers" width="1170" height="658" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iQeaK0NGMnA?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>Sorry to tell you, but if you see <strong>5G E</strong>, you are not on a 5G network. This symbol is fake 5G, and in fact, you&#8217;re connected to an LTE Advanced network. You may see faster speeds than a typical 4G network but nowhere near 5G or 5G+. Unfortunately, Android 11 had added this symbol, and AT&amp;T already includes this icon in the status bar of several phones.</p>



<p>Intel, however, is not able to match Qualcomm’s 5G prowess, and won’t have 5G modems ready for 2019 devices. Apple is also at work on building its own modems, but it will likely be many years before it’s able to use its own in-house chips. As for using 5G modems from the likes of Samsung and Huawei — Apple isn’t likely to go into business with direct competitors. Its best (and only) option is waiting until 2020 to use Intel’s 5G modems.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/what-5g-icon-shown-in-your-status-bar-really-means/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Artificial Intelligence (AI)</title>
		<link>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/artificial-intelligence-ai/</link>
					<comments>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/artificial-intelligence-ai/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siteadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 11:12:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[AI]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Artificial Inteligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[-future-evolution-of-humans-with-help-of-ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ai]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial inteligence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[artificial-intelligence-and-algorithums]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[role-of-artificial-inteligence-in-our-futre]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gadgethackz.tk/?p=22</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Technology is evolving at fast pace as it looks like it will take over in many fields in the world and it feels like worker have to be skilled with &#8230; <a href="https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/artificial-intelligence-ai/" class="more-link">Read More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><img class="wp-image-23" style="width: 1022px;" src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/artificial_intelligence_benefits_risk-1400x430-1.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/artificial_intelligence_benefits_risk-1400x430-1.jpg 1400w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/artificial_intelligence_benefits_risk-1400x430-1-300x92.jpg 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/artificial_intelligence_benefits_risk-1400x430-1-1024x315.jpg 1024w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/artificial_intelligence_benefits_risk-1400x430-1-768x236.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px" />Technology is evolving at fast pace as it looks like it will take over in many fields in the world and it feels like worker have to be skilled with technology otherwise unemployment would be at its peak. As technology is evolving it enables the fast progress and change, causing acceleration and working as catalyst at the rate of change. Eventually, it is going to become exponential. Career which are based on technology are not going to change rapidly as technology has replaced other old working methods.</p>



<h2>Challenges</h2>



<div class="wp-block-group"><div class="wp-block-group__inner-container">
<p>The cognitive capabilities of current architectures are very limited, using only a simplified version of what intelligence is really capable of. For instance, the human mind has come up with ways to reason beyond measure and logical explanations to different occurrences in life. What would have been otherwise straightforward, an equivalently difficult problem may be challenging to solve computationally as opposed to using the human mind. This gives rise to two classes of models: structuralist and functionalist. The structural models aim to loosely mimic the basic intelligence operations of the mind such as reasoning and logic. The functional model refers to the correlating data to its computed counterpart.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence#cite_note-88">[85]</a></sup><img class="wp-image-24" style="width: 788px;" src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/artificial-intelligence-education.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/artificial-intelligence-education.jpg 1021w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/artificial-intelligence-education-300x170.jpg 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/artificial-intelligence-education-768x436.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1021px) 100vw, 1021px" /></p>
</div></div>



<p>The overall research goal of artificial intelligence is to create technology that allows computers and machines to function in an intelligent manner. The general problem of simulating (or creating) intelligence has been broken down into sub-problems. These consist of particular traits or capabilities that researchers expect an intelligent system to display. The traits described below have received the most attention.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence#cite_note-Problems_of_AI-16">[16]</a></sup></p>



<h3>Reasoning, problem solving</h3>



<p>Early researchers developed algorithms that imitated step-by-step reasoning that humans use when they solve puzzles or make logical deductions.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence#cite_note-Reasoning-89">[86]</a></sup> By the late 1980s and 1990s, AI research had developed methods for dealing with <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uncertainty">uncertain</a> or incomplete information, employing concepts from <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Probability">probability</a> and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Economics">economics</a>.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence#cite_note-Uncertain_reasoning-90">[87]</a></sup></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="What is AI (Artificial Intelligence)?" width="1170" height="658" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/0oRVLf16CMU?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>These algorithms proved to be insufficient for solving large reasoning problems because they experienced a &#8220;combinatorial explosion&#8221;: they became exponentially slower as the problems grew larger.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence#cite_note-Intractability-69">[67]</a></sup> Even humans rarely use the step-by-step deduction that early AI research could model. They solve most of their problems using fast, intuitive judgments.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence#cite_note-Psychological_evidence_of_sub-symbolic_reasoning-91">[88]</a></sup></p>



<p>What does it mean for the people who aren’t related to IT field? It means staying Up-To-Date with technology and follows its trends. It means everyone would have to keep an eye on the changing tends of world, to know that what kind of skills they would need in future and what kind of jobs are going to be created in near future with technology development. Here is a latest technology about which we are going to talk about which is in trend and going to create a lot of jobs for the skilled people.</p>



<p><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Default_reasoning">Default reasoning</a> and the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Qualification_problem">qualification problem</a> Many of the things people know take the form of &#8220;working assumptions&#8221;. For example, if a bird comes up in conversation, people typically picture a fist-sized animal that sings and flies. None of these things are true about all birds. <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_McCarthy_(computer_scientist)">John McCarthy</a> identified this problem in 1969<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence#cite_note-Qualification_problem-105">[102]</a></sup> as the qualification problem: for any commonsense rule that AI researchers care to represent, there tend to be a huge number of exceptions. Almost nothing is simply true or false in the way that abstract logic requires. AI research has explored a number of solutions to this problem.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence#cite_note-Default_reasoning_and_non-monotonic_logic-106">[103]</a></sup></p>



<p>Artificial Intelligence (AI) has already been increased in last some years. It is trending in recent times because it has effects on how we work, live, and play only in early stages. In addition, other branches of AI have developed, including Machine Learning, Robotic Process Automation, but we will talk about these in some other articles. AI works with computer systems to build or intimate the human intelligence and it perform the tasks like speech or patterns, decision making, and recognition of images. AI can do the tasks faster and more precisely than humans as per accurate directions.</p>



<p>Almost five out of six Americans use AI services in one or other form on daily basis, including streaming services, navigation apps, personal smartphone assistants, ride-sharing apps, smart home devices, and home personal assistants. In addition AI is used to assess business risk, schedule trains, predict maintenance, and improve the energy efficiency, and among much other money-saving works to be done.AI can broadly be referred as automation, and the automation is one of hot topic these days &nbsp;job loss in many fields because of recent pandemic situation. Experts say that automation is going to decrease 73 million more jobs for workers by 2030. However, automation is increasing job opportunities as well as eliminating them, especially in the field of AI million by the end of 2020. Jobs will be created in programming, development, support, maintenance, and testing. Artificial Intelligence architect is one such job. Some say it will soon rival data scientists in need of skilled professionals. AI is creating more jobs in these days because people are sitting at homes so that they can work from home if they have any skills or they can have an AI certification to get jobs or get skilled with this evolving field.</p>

1f78
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/artificial-intelligence-ai/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Increase in domestic violence in women during COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/increase-in-domestic-violence-in-women-during-covid-19/</link>
					<comments>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/increase-in-domestic-violence-in-women-during-covid-19/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siteadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 10:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[COVID 19]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[António Guterres]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[domestic voilence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[domestic voilence during covid 19]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[united nations security general tweets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gadgethackz.tk/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[COVID-19 has changed the entire world. It bought a lot of other things with its pandemic nature.  Whether it took a positive change in climate , because the traffic and &#8230; <a href="https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/increase-in-domestic-violence-in-women-during-covid-19/" class="more-link">Read More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>COVID-19 has changed the entire world. It bought a lot of other things with its pandemic nature.  Whether it took a positive change in climate , because the traffic and the flights in the whole world has decreased due to lockdown since April 2020.But here is a problem of domestic violence which has been increased in this situation of lockdown. Yes, the violence was there in every form but the cases of domestic violence were not in this ratio which has been increased rapidly in the whole world.<img class="wp-image-16" style="width: 864px;" src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449.png" alt="" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449.png 1920w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449-300x180.png 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449-1024x614.png 1024w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449-768x461.png 768w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449-1536x922.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /></p>



<p>According to Violence Against Women Grant the existing crisis of violence is likely to be worse in this COVID-19. Data shows that since the start of COVID-19, reports about  violence against women, and particularly the domestic violence, have increased in many countries as health, security, and financial worries has created  tensions and strains intensified  by the confined living conditions of lockdown. More than half of the world’s population was under lockdown conditions by early April.  Countries like France, Singapore and Cyprus has reported 30 percent increase in their domestic violence according to their helpline.</p>



<p><strong>Interpersonal violence rises in times of crisis</strong></p>



<p>Increases in interpersonal violence during times of crisis are well documented. But wide underreporting has made response and data gathering a challenge, with less than 40 per cent of women who experience violence seeking any help or reporting the crime. &nbsp;Of those women who do seek help, less than 10 per cent go to the police.</p>



<p>However, early data shows that helplines in Singapore and Cyprus have registered a more than 30 per cent increase in calls. &nbsp;In Australia, 40 per cent of frontline workers in New South Wales reported more requests for help with violence. &nbsp;In France, domestic violence cases increased by 30 per cent since the lockdown on March 17. &nbsp;In Argentina, emergency calls for domestic violence have increased by 25 per cent since the lockdown on March 20.</p>



<p>“Unfortunately, every country in the region is already all too familiar with the scourge of interpersonal violence”, says the World Health Organization (WHO)  Regional Office for Europe.in united Kingdom the national domestic violence charity, have increased 97 per cent, 185 per cent and 581 per cent respectively.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-twitter wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Peace is not just the absence of war. Many women under lockdown for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/COVID19?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#COVID19</a> face violence where they should be safest: in their own homes.<br><br>Today I appeal for peace in homes around the world.<br><br>I urge all governments to put women’s safety first as they respond to the pandemic. <a href="https://t.co/PjDUTrMb9v">pic.twitter.com/PjDUTrMb9v</a></p>&mdash; António Guterres (@antonioguterres) <a href="https://twitter.com/antonioguterres/status/1246973397759819776?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 6, 2020</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>In <a href="https://www.un.org/en/un-coronavirus-communications-team/make-prevention-and-redress-violence-against-women-key-part">his message</a>, UN Secretary-General António Guterres said that for many women and girls, the COVID-19 threat looms largest where they should be safest – their own homes. &nbsp;“We know lockdowns and quarantines are essential to suppressing COVID-19,” he said.&nbsp; However “they can trap women with abusive partners.”</p>



<p>He urged all Governments to make the prevention and redress of violence against women a key part of their national response plans.  Governments allover the world have supported his call.</p>



<p>From a hurricane in New Orleans to war in Syria, domestic violence increases when communities face crisis. We should know that COVID-19 is no exception. Stress and anxiety brought on by the outbreak can leave an abuser feeling out of control, triggering violence. And the measures we’ve taken to control the disease create more danger. Distancing from those outside the family reinforces the isolation that abusers impose. Suspension of work means many more hours of exposure to violence at home. Lockdown cuts off avenues of escape.</p>



<p>We’ve begun to see reports about the pandemic triggering domestic violence in some of the world’s centers of power. France and the United.States. for example, are reporting spikes in domestic violence calls to hotlines. In China, the number of cases reported to police nearly tripled in February, the peak month for COVID-19, compared to last year.<img class="wp-image-20" style="width: 1200px;" src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/gettyimages-5139573681_0.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/gettyimages-5139573681_0.jpg 955w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/gettyimages-5139573681_0-300x157.jpg 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/gettyimages-5139573681_0-768x402.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 955px) 100vw, 955px" /></p>



<p>In Germany, Canada, Spain, the United stated, and the United kingdom, women’s rights activists  , government authorities, and civil society partners have declared the increasing reports of domestic violence during this crisis, and increased in demand for emergency shelter. Even in Pakistan there is an massive increase in domestic violence due to lockdown. Men have to remain at homes and doing nothing and financial strains are creating the stress and the results in form of violence on their spouse. According to THE NEWS there is an increase in domestic violence bur is not reported because of fair of society and lack of knowledge. Now the question is who is the responsible for all this increasing violence? . Who will tell women about their basic rights?</p>

38bb
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/increase-in-domestic-violence-in-women-during-covid-19/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hexxa Plus Online Jailbreak is just released for iOS 13.5.1</title>
		<link>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hexxa-plus-online-jailbreak-is-just-released-for-ios-13-5-1/</link>
					<comments>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hexxa-plus-online-jailbreak-is-just-released-for-ios-13-5-1/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siteadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 09:03:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[iphone]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[how to jailbreak ios 13 with hexa plux]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone 13]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[iphone jailbreak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[no computer jailbreak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uncover jailbreak]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uncover jailbreak for ios 13.5]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[with out computer iphone jailbreak]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gadgethackz.tk/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Install awesome jailbreak Apps, collection of themes, you can alos install the apps banned from app store.its also good if you want to install + Install Awesome Jailbreak apps + &#8230; <a href="https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hexxa-plus-online-jailbreak-is-just-released-for-ios-13-5-1/" class="more-link">Read More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Install awesome jailbreak Apps, collection of themes, you can alos install the apps banned from app store.its also good if you want to install </p>



<p>+ Install Awesome Jailbreak apps</p>



<p>+ Collection of Themes</p>



<p>+ App store banned apps/games</p>



<p>+ Premium ++ Apps</p>



<p>+ Game Emulators</p>



<p> </p>



<p>Apple fixed unc0ver Jailbreak releasing iOS 13.5.1. However, Hexxa Plus repo extractor was released for iOS 13.5.1. Now you can install jailbreak apps / tweaks for iOS 13.5.1 extracting Jailbreak repos.</p>



<p>Hexxa Plus is different from Unc0ver semi untethered Jailbreak. Hexxa Plus Installation process is so much easier than IPA based Unc0ver or checkm8 based Checkrain. But all system related Jailbreak apps and tweaks are not available for iOS 13.5.1 via Hexxa Plus.</p>



<p><strong><a href="https://hexxaplus.com/install/latest/app/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">DOWONLOAD HEXA PLUS</a></strong></p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<iframe title="Hexaa+ iOS 13 Jailbreak (New Update) 2019" width="1170" height="658" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YhFFf5fctVM?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
</div></figure>



<p>Currently Hexxa Plus is the only iOS 13.5.1 Jailbreak solution. You can install so many Jailbreak apps, tweaks and themes using this. Now it is compatible to install jailbreak apps for iOS 14 as well.&nbsp;</p>



<p><strong>Compatibility&nbsp;</strong></p>



<p>iPhone 11, 11 pro, 11 pro max, iPhone Xs, iPhone Xs Max, iPhone Xr, iPhone X, iPhone 8, iPhone 8 Plus, Phone 7 &amp; 7 Plus, iPhone 6S &amp; 6S Plus, iPhone 6 &amp; 6 Plus, iPhone SE, iPad Mini (5th gen), iPad Air (2019, 3rd gen), iPad Pro 2nd gen &amp; 1st gen, iPad Pro, iPad Air 2, iPad Air, iPad 6th gen, iPad 5th gen, iPad mini 4, iPad mini 3, iPad mini 2, iPod Touch 6G</p>



<ul><li>Hexxa Plus is not a semi untethered or tethered Jailbreak solution. That’s mean It doesn’t affect your iOS system room.&nbsp;</li><li>Hexxa Plus is compatible with all latest device models such as iPhone 11 series and iPhone XS series.</li><li>You don’t need to use a computer, iTunes or Cydia impactor to install Hexxa Plus. There is no IPA sideload process. Hexxa Plus is a completely online jailbreak solution.&nbsp;</li><li>Hexxa Plus is a 100% risk free iOS 13.5.1 jailbreak solution. You can uninstall / reinstall it any time. Also, no crash your iOS device once reboot.&nbsp;</li><li>Hexxa Plus does not void your iOS device warranty.&nbsp;</li><li>Recently, Hexxa Plus upgraded, adding many new repostaries. You can install many Jailbreak apps and tweaks using these repostaries.</li></ul>



<h2><strong>Unc0ver Jailbreak for iOS 13.5.1</strong></h2>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/uncover1351.png" alt="" class="wp-image-8" width="922" height="346" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/uncover1351.png 800w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/uncover1351-300x113.png 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/uncover1351-768x288.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 922px) 100vw, 922px" /></figure>



<p>pple fixed the uncover Jailbreak for iOS 13.5.1 releasing iOS 13.5.1 version. Now Unc0ver latest version doesn’t support iOS 13.5.1. However, the Unc0ver team is working on a new Unc0ver exploit that could jailbreak iOS 13.5.1.</p>



<p>Uncover is the most popular Jailbreak tool since iOS 11. However, when it comes to iOS 13 – iOS 13.5 Jailbreak it has some issues. There is no Online jailbreak which properly works. It is getting revoked issues. Also, it has a complicated JB process using the alt store on Mac &amp; Windows users. Also, it should have an Apple developer account to complete the Jailbreak method for linux users to work with the Cydia Impactor.</p>



<p><strong>CheckRain Jailbreak for iOS 13.5.1</strong></p>



<p>Checkra1n is hardware based jailbreak for iOS 12.3 – iOS 13.5 jailbreak. This works with iOS 13.5.1 too because it can not be fixed via software update. They will add iOS 13.5.1 jailbreak support via next checkra1n 0.10.3 beta officially.</p>



<p>One of the reasons for jailbreaking is to expand the feature set limited by Apple and its App Store.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-ars-2">[2]</a></sup> Apple checks apps for compliance with its iOS Developer Program License Agreement before accepting them for distribution in the App Store. However, their reasons for banning apps are not limited to safety and security and may be regarded as arbitrary and capricious.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-3">[3]</a></sup> In one case, Apple mistakenly banned an app by a Pulitzer-Winning cartoonist because it violated its developer license agreement, which specifically bans apps that &#8220;contain content that ridicules public figures.&#8221;<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-4">[4]</a></sup> To access banned apps,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-5">[5]</a></sup> users rely on jailbreaking to circumvent Apple&#8217;s censorship of content and features. Jailbreaking permits the downloading of programs not approved by Apple,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-6">[6]</a></sup> such as user interface customization and tweaks.</p>



<h3>Device customization</h3>



<p>Since software programs available through <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/APT_(Package_Manager)">APT</a> and or <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Installer.app">Installer.app</a> (legacy) are not required to adhere to App Store guidelines, many of them are not typical self-contained apps but instead are extensions and customization options for iOS and its features and other apps (commonly called tweaks).<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-lifehacker-dachis-7">[7]</a></sup> Users install these programs for purposes including personalization and customization of the interface by tweaks developed by developers and designers,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-lifehacker-dachis-7">[7]</a></sup> adding desired features such as access to the root file system and fixing annoyances,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-nytimes-8">[8]</a></sup> and making development work on the device easier by providing access to the filesystem and command-line tools.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-9">[9]</a></sup><sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-10">[10]</a></sup> Many Chinese iOS device owners also jailbreak their phones to install third-party <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chinese_input_methods_for_computers">Chinese</a> character <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Input_method">input systems</a> because they are easier to use than Apple&#8217;s.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-11">[11]</a></sup></p>



<h3>Carrier unlocking</h3>



<p>Jailbreaking also opens the possibility for using <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Software">software</a> to unofficially unlock <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SIM_lock">carrier-locked</a> iPhones so they can be used with other carriers.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-12">[12]</a></sup> Software-based unlocks have been available since September 2007,<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-13">[13]</a></sup> with each tool applying to a specific iPhone model and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baseband_processor">baseband</a> version (or multiple models and versions).<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-14">[14]</a></sup> This includes the <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_4S">iPhone 4S</a>, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_4">iPhone 4</a>, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_3GS">iPhone 3GS</a>, and <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPhone_3G">iPhone 3G</a> models. An example of unlocking an iPhone through a Jailbreak utility would be Redsn0w. Through this software, iPhone users will be able to create a custom <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IPSW">IPSW</a> and unlock their device. Moreover, during the unlocking process, there are options to install Cydia the iPad baseband.</p>



<h3>Installation of malware</h3>



<p>Computer criminals may jailbreak an iPhone to install malware or target jailbroken iPhones on which malware can be installed more easily. The Italian cybersecurity company Hacking Team, which sells hacking software to law enforcement agencies, advised police to jailbreak iPhones to allow tracking software to be installed on them.</p>



<h3>Software piracy</h3>



<p>On iPhones, the installation of consumer software is generally restricted to installation through the App Store. Jailbreaking, therefore, allows the installation of pirated applications.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-17">[17]</a></sup> It has been suggested that a major motivation for Apple to prevent jailbreaking is to protect the income of its App Store, including third-party developers and allow the buildup of a sustainable market for third-party software.<sup><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/IOS_jailbreaking#cite_note-18">[18]</a></sup> However, the installation of pirated applications is also possible without jailbreaking, taking advantage of enterprise certificates to facilitate distribution of modified or pirated releases of popular applications</p>



<p></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large is-resized"><img src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/check1351-1024x384-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-9" width="927" height="348" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/check1351-1024x384-1.png 1024w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/check1351-1024x384-1-300x113.png 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/check1351-1024x384-1-768x288.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 927px) 100vw, 927px" /></figure>



<p>However, it has some limitations. This checkra1n works only for A5-A11 devices. Latest iPhone 11 models and iPhone Xs models do not work with Checkra1n. On the other hand, there is no online jailbreak method for Checkra1n. Also, Windows users have to use alternative complicated method to run checkra1n Jailbreak process.</p>



<h2><strong>without computer or No Computer online Jailbreak</strong></h2>



<p>Hexxa plus is the only online jailbreak solution for iOS 13.5.1.</p>



<p>Apple blocks online plist IPA for semi-untethered Jailbreak. Once reported, these signing services to Apple, the company immediately revoked licenses. Once these licenses are revoked, it is required to set up a new account to resign every application on that platform. This process takes a long time.</p>



<p>At this moment, all unc0ver enterprise certificates are revoked and blocked by Apple. Many websites such as silzee, ignition.fun, tweakbox have stopped providing enterprise certificate based online Jailbreak. So, no computer;online Jailbreak for previous Unc0ver versions too.&nbsp;</p>



<p>So if unc0ver releases iOS 13.5.1 Jailbreak, permanent online Jailbreaking will be almost impossible.</p>



<p>Last Unc0ver Jailbreak works with Windows, Mac with the Altstore and Cydia impactor. Also, linux works only with Cydia impactor. You need to sideload the IPA using Altstore or Cydia impactor. Both this method required Computer. This Altstore is introduced because Cydia impactor works with Paid Certificate only. So, you need an Apple developer account. Linux users have no other option except Cydia impactor.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Checkra1n is a computer based Jailbreak. There is No Computer online Jailbreak for CheckRa1n.Mac users have to download the Checkra1n dmg file and Connect the Mac and the device.&nbsp; Then it should recognize the device going through&nbsp; Mac’s application folder &gt; checkra1n &gt; Contents &gt; MacOS &gt; Checkra1n_gui Terminal file. Once done it can complete the jailbreak process with DFU mode.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Also, Linux users have to download the linux file according to the computer version and run commands using the terminal window. Windows users have to years alternative methods somewhat hard Ra1nUSB, Ra1nstorm, Bootra1n or pira1n. Ultimately we can not expect CheckRa1n online jailbreak for iOS 13.5.1 versions too.&nbsp;</p>

443
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hexxa-plus-online-jailbreak-is-just-released-for-ios-13-5-1/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siteadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 08:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gadgethackz.tk/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

0

