2255
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>António Guterres &#8211; GaDgetHackz</title>
	<atom:link href="https://gadgethackz.tk/tag/antonio-guterres/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://gadgethackz.tk</link>
	<description>Gadget Hacks » Smartphone Lifehacks, Guides, Tips, Tricks &#38; How-Tos</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 10:51:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.4.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Increase in domestic violence in women during COVID-19</title>
		<link>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/increase-in-domestic-violence-in-women-during-covid-19/</link>
					<comments>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/increase-in-domestic-violence-in-women-during-covid-19/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[siteadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2020 10:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[COVID 19]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[António Guterres]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[domestic voilence]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[domestic voilence during covid 19]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[united nations security general tweets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://gadgethackz.tk/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[COVID-19 has changed the entire world. It bought a lot of other things with its pandemic nature.  Whether it took a positive change in climate , because the traffic and &#8230; <a href="https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/increase-in-domestic-violence-in-women-during-covid-19/" class="more-link">Read More</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>COVID-19 has changed the entire world. It bought a lot of other things with its pandemic nature.  Whether it took a positive change in climate , because the traffic and the flights in the whole world has decreased due to lockdown since April 2020.But here is a problem of domestic violence which has been increased in this situation of lockdown. Yes, the violence was there in every form but the cases of domestic violence were not in this ratio which has been increased rapidly in the whole world.<img class="wp-image-16" style="width: 864px;" src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449.png" alt="" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449.png 1920w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449-300x180.png 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449-1024x614.png 1024w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449-768x461.png 768w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/2449-1536x922.png 1536w" sizes="(max-width: 1920px) 100vw, 1920px" /></p>



<p>According to Violence Against Women Grant the existing crisis of violence is likely to be worse in this COVID-19. Data shows that since the start of COVID-19, reports about  violence against women, and particularly the domestic violence, have increased in many countries as health, security, and financial worries has created  tensions and strains intensified  by the confined living conditions of lockdown. More than half of the world’s population was under lockdown conditions by early April.  Countries like France, Singapore and Cyprus has reported 30 percent increase in their domestic violence according to their helpline.</p>



<p><strong>Interpersonal violence rises in times of crisis</strong></p>



<p>Increases in interpersonal violence during times of crisis are well documented. But wide underreporting has made response and data gathering a challenge, with less than 40 per cent of women who experience violence seeking any help or reporting the crime. &nbsp;Of those women who do seek help, less than 10 per cent go to the police.</p>



<p>However, early data shows that helplines in Singapore and Cyprus have registered a more than 30 per cent increase in calls. &nbsp;In Australia, 40 per cent of frontline workers in New South Wales reported more requests for help with violence. &nbsp;In France, domestic violence cases increased by 30 per cent since the lockdown on March 17. &nbsp;In Argentina, emergency calls for domestic violence have increased by 25 per cent since the lockdown on March 20.</p>



<p>“Unfortunately, every country in the region is already all too familiar with the scourge of interpersonal violence”, says the World Health Organization (WHO)  Regional Office for Europe.in united Kingdom the national domestic violence charity, have increased 97 per cent, 185 per cent and 581 per cent respectively.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed-twitter wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Peace is not just the absence of war. Many women under lockdown for <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/COVID19?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#COVID19</a> face violence where they should be safest: in their own homes.<br><br>Today I appeal for peace in homes around the world.<br><br>I urge all governments to put women’s safety first as they respond to the pandemic. <a href="https://t.co/PjDUTrMb9v">pic.twitter.com/PjDUTrMb9v</a></p>&mdash; António Guterres (@antonioguterres) <a href="https://twitter.com/antonioguterres/status/1246973397759819776?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 6, 2020</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>In <a href="https://www.un.org/en/un-coronavirus-communications-team/make-prevention-and-redress-violence-against-women-key-part">his message</a>, UN Secretary-General António Guterres said that for many women and girls, the COVID-19 threat looms largest where they should be safest – their own homes. &nbsp;“We know lockdowns and quarantines are essential to suppressing COVID-19,” he said.&nbsp; However “they can trap women with abusive partners.”</p>



<p>He urged all Governments to make the prevention and redress of violence against women a key part of their national response plans.  Governments allover the world have supported his call.</p>



<p>From a hurricane in New Orleans to war in Syria, domestic violence increases when communities face crisis. We should know that COVID-19 is no exception. Stress and anxiety brought on by the outbreak can leave an abuser feeling out of control, triggering violence. And the measures we’ve taken to control the disease create more danger. Distancing from those outside the family reinforces the isolation that abusers impose. Suspension of work means many more hours of exposure to violence at home. Lockdown cuts off avenues of escape.</p>



<p>We’ve begun to see reports about the pandemic triggering domestic violence in some of the world’s centers of power. France and the United.States. for example, are reporting spikes in domestic violence calls to hotlines. In China, the number of cases reported to police nearly tripled in February, the peak month for COVID-19, compared to last year.<img class="wp-image-20" style="width: 1200px;" src="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/gettyimages-5139573681_0.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/gettyimages-5139573681_0.jpg 955w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/gettyimages-5139573681_0-300x157.jpg 300w, https://gadgethackz.tk/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/gettyimages-5139573681_0-768x402.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 955px) 100vw, 955px" /></p>



<p>In Germany, Canada, Spain, the United stated, and the United kingdom, women’s rights activists  , government authorities, and civil society partners have declared the increasing reports of domestic violence during this crisis, and increased in demand for emergency shelter. Even in Pakistan there is an massive increase in domestic violence due to lockdown. Men have to remain at homes and doing nothing and financial strains are creating the stress and the results in form of violence on their spouse. According to THE NEWS there is an increase in domestic violence bur is not reported because of fair of society and lack of knowledge. Now the question is who is the responsible for all this increasing violence? . Who will tell women about their basic rights?</p>

ee
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://gadgethackz.tk/2020/07/02/increase-in-domestic-violence-in-women-during-covid-19/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

0

